http://www.spacedesign.co.uk/cookie-policy

Cookie Policy
Home  »
Cookie Policy
What are cookies:
We and our business partners collect information about your use of our website through cookies. Cookies are information files stored on your computer, tablet or smartphone that help websites remember who you are and information about your visit. Cookies can help to display the information on a website in a way that matches your interests. Most major websites use cookies.
What cookies are used on this Website:
The cookies we and our business partners use on this website are broadly grouped into the following categories:
Essential â€“ Some of the cookies on our website are essential for us to be able to provide you with a service you have requested. An example of this would be a cookie used to enable you to log into your account on the website or which allows communication between your browser and the website. Our cookie preference cookie described in the section “How can I reject or opt out of receiving cookies?” is also an essential cookie. You may not be able to use our website without these cookies.
Analytics â€“ We use analytics cookies to helps us understand how users engage with our website. An example is counting the number of different people coming to our website or using a particular feature, rather than the total number of times the site or feature is used. Without this cookie, if you visited the website once each week for three weeks we would count you as three separate users. We would find it difficult to analyse how well our website was performing and improve it without these cookies.
Social Sharing â€“ We use cookies to allow you to share content directly on the social networking/sharing sites like Facebook, Twitter or Google+. Examples would be if you wanted to “like” or “tweet” about a business or product advertised on our website.
Interest-Based Advertising â€“ You will have noticed that when you visit websites you will be shown adverts for products and services you may wish to buy. The money made by website owners for showing third party adverts on their websites often pays for the cost of running the website and therefore usually allows you to use the website without having to pay a registration or usage fee. We, like many businesses may place adverts for ourselves on a range of associated websites. However, to try and ensure that the adverts you see are relevant to you we use cookies to collect information about the types of things that interest you, for example websites you visit and the geography that you are based in. Having these cookies does not increase the number of adverts you will be shown, but simply makes the adverts you see more relevant.
How can I reject or opt out of receiving cookies?
When you first visited this website you will have been shown a message bar drawing your attention to the fact that this website uses cookies and inviting you to review this cookie policy to help manage your cookie preferences. If you do not manage your preferences despite this prompt a cookie preference cookie will be dropped confirming that you consent to us using the cookies detailed in this cookie policy, this cookie preference cookie will last for no more than 5 years.
Please note that we can’t always control third party cookies stored on your machine from our website and where this is the case you will need to visit the relevant third party’s website directly to manage cookies stored on your machine by them. Please see our “Third Party Cookies” section below.
If you want to reject cookies we use from this website you will need to:
delete the cookies from your browser. Most browsers also allow you to prevent all or some cookies being stored on your machine in the future. For more information on how to delete or disable cookies from your browser please use the “help” function within your browser or alternatively visit www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookie preference cookie the next time you visit this website the cookie message bar will appear again inviting you to again reconsider your preferences; and/or
if you only want to reject some or all of the third party cookies you will need to visit the relevant third party’s website directly to manage cookies stored on your machine by them. Please see our “Third Party Cookies” section below
Please be aware that disabling cookies may impact the functionality of this website.
Third party cookies:
Some of the cookies described in the “What Cookies are used on this Website” section above are stored on your machine by third parties when you use our website. We have no control over these cookies or how the third parties use them. They are used to allow that third party to provide a service to us, for example analytics. For more information on these cookies and how to disable them, please see:
Internet Advertising Bureau website at http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ where you will be able to opt-out of receiving Interest-Based Advertising cookies from some of the third parties listed below; and/or
the third party’s individual privacy policy listed below:
Third Party
Type of cookies
More Info.
Adobe / Omniture
Analytics
Omniture provide anonymised data about the visits made to our website and allows us to test and evaluate the best ways to present our website to our users.
Privacy Policy
Google
Analytics
Google provides anonymised data about the visits made to our website.Social SharingGoogle also store cookies which allow the “Google +” social sharing functionality.
Privacy Policy
AddThis
Analytics
AddThis provides anonymised data about how many users are sharing content on our website.
Social Sharing
AddThis store cookies which allow the social sharing functionality on social networks such as Facebook.
Interest-Based Advertising
AddThis tools may also collect data for the purpose of interest-based advertising.
Privacy Policy
Facebook
Social Sharing
Facebook store cookies which allow the Facebook “Like” social sharing functionality but only if you click on the Facebook “Like” button on our website or log in to hibu using your Facebook account.
Privacy Policy
Twitter
Social Sharing
Twitter also store cookies which allow their social sharing functionality including the “Tweet” function and to generate usage information during your visit to our website.
Privacy Policy
eBay / Doubleclick
Interest-Based Advertising
eBay may have cookies dropped on their behalf in order to collect data for the purpose of interest-based advertising.
Privacy Policy
AOL
Interest-Based Advertising
AOL cookies may also collect data for the purpose of interest-based advertising.
Privacy Policy
iPromote
Interest-Based Advertising
iPromote cookies also collect data for the purpose of interest-based advertising.
Privacy Policy
If you want to know more about how cookies work and how to manage or delete them, visit the World Wide Web Consortium’s website.
We may update this policy from time to time so you may want to check it each time you visit our website. We last changed this policy on 28 October 2013.
